{"name":"M21_02_Variablen 2","currentQuestionIndex":-1,"questionList":[{"questionText":"Gegeben sei die Zahl 15\nWelchen der folgenden Datentypen würden Sie benutzen","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":1,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"int","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"double","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"char","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"boolean","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Gegeben sei die Zahl 12.5\nWelchen der folgenden Datentypen würden Sie benutzen?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":1,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"int","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"float","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"char","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"boolean","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Gegeben sei das Zeichen '$'.\nWelchen der folgenden Datentypen würden Sie benutzen?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":1,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"int","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"double","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"char","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"boolean","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Name the data type: \"true\"","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"boolean","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"char","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"String","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"double","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Name the data type: 1.0","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"double","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"int","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"char","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"boolean","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Name the data type: '3'","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"int","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"char","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"String","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"None of the above","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Name the data type: false","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"String","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"boolean","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"int","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"None of the above","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"What data type would you use for storing the number of students in a class?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"boolean","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"String","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"double","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"int","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"What data type would you use for storing the average test score in a class?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"double","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"String","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"int","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"char","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"What data type would you use for storing letter grades (without - or +) for students in a class?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"String","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"int","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"boolean","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"char","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"What data type would you use to store names of students?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"String","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"char","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"boolean","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"None of these","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"How would you declare a variable storing a person's name?\n","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"string name = \"Jeff\";","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"String name = Jeff;","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"name String = \"Jeff\";","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"String name = \"Jeff\";","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"How would you declare a variable storing the tax rate?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"int taxRate = 5.1;","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"taxRate = \"5.1\";","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"double taxRate = 5.1;","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"double taxRate = \"5.1\";","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"How would you declare a variable that tells you that someone passed a class?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"boolean passed = 'true';","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"boolean passed = true;","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"passed = true;","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"String passed = \"true\";","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Which declaration will throw an error?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"double num = 8;","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"int averageGrade = 89.7;","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"boolean done = false;","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"String done = \"true\";","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"What prints out \"I love Java\" successfully?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"System.out.println(I love Java);","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Systemoutprintln(\"I love Java);","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"System.out.println(\"I love\" + \" Java\");","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"System.out.println(\"I love Java\")","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Name the data type: \"true\"","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"boolean","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"char","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"String","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"double","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Which of the following is NOT a primitive data type?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"int","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"double","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"boolean","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"String","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"What data type should we use to hold the name of your favorite color?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"int","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"double","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"boolean","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"String","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"What data type should we use to hold if you have a pet?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"int","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"double","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"boolean","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"String","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"True or false:\n\nThis is a correct initialization of a variable.\n\n\nint numBooks = 6;","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"True or false:\n\nThis is a correct initialization of a variable.\n\n\nint myTemperature = 98.2;","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"True or false:\n\nThis is a correct initialization of a variable.\n\n\nString name = Bob;","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"True or false:\n\nThis is a correct initialization of a variable.\n\n\nString favoriteDay = \"Saturday\";","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"True or false:\n\nThis is a correct initialization of a variable.\n\n\nboolean happy = true;","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"true","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"false","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Which is the correct statement for output in Java?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"system.out.print();","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"System.out.println();","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"System.Out.Printf();","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"System.out.show();","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Which is the correct way to define a String variable?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"String name = \"John\";","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"String name = John;","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"String name = \"John\"","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"String name \"John\";","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Which statement about choosing variable names is FALSE?\n\nA. Variable names can contain letters, digits, underscores, and dollar signs.\n\nB. Variable names are NOT case sensitive\n\nC. Reserved words (like Java keywords, such as int or String) cannot be used as variable names\n\nD. Variable names can also begin with $ and _","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"A","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"B","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"C","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"D","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Which of the following is the correct way of defining a char variable?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"char myGrade = \"B\";","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"char myGrade 'B';","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"char myGrade = \"B\"","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"char myGrade = 'B';","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Which one is a valid declaration of boolean?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"boolean b1 = 1;","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"boolean b2 = 'false';","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"boolean b3 = false;","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"boolean b4 = 'true'","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"How many primitive data types are there in Java programming?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"3","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"5","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"8","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"What prints out \"I love Java\" successfully?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"System.out.println(I love Java);","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Systemoutprintln(\"I love Java);","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"System.out.println(\"I love\" + \" Java\");","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"System.out.println(\"I love Java\")","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Which declaration will throw an error?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"double num = 8;","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"boolean done = false;","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"int averageGrade = 89.7;","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"String done = \"true\";","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Which declaration with throw an error?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"String name = \"1 1233 141\";","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"double num = 1;","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"int bigNumber = 1234567890;","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"char random = '7';","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"What of the following is the default value of an instance variable?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"Null","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"0","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Depens upton the type of variable","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Not assigned","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"What is the default value of the String variable? ","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"\"","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"\"\"","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Null","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Not defined","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Which one of these is NOT a valid name for a Java variable?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"myAge","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"MyAge","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"my#hashtag","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"my_hashtag","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"How do you insert COMMENTS in Java code?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"/* This is a comment","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"#This is a comment","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"// This is a comment","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"Which data type is used to create a variable that should store text?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"myString","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"string","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"Txt","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"String","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"How do you create a variable with the numeric value 5?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"float x = 5;","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"num x = 5","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"x = 5","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"int x = 5;","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"How do you create a variable with the floating number 2.8?","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"byte x = 2.8f","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"int x = 2.8f;","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"x = 2.8f;","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"float x = 2.8f;","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"},{"questionText":"The value of a string variable can be surrounded by single quotes ' '","timer":100,"displayAnswerText":true,"tags":[],"requiredForToken":true,"difficulty":5,"answerOptionList":[{"answerText":"False","isCorrect":true,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"},{"answerText":"True","isCorrect":false,"TYPE":"DefaultAnswerOption"}],"showOneAnswerPerRow":true,"TYPE":"SingleChoiceQuestion"}],"sessionConfig":{"theme":"Material","readingConfirmationEnabled":false,"showResponseProgress":true,"confidenceSliderEnabled":false,"music":{"enabled":{"lobby":true,"countdownRunning":true,"countdownEnd":true},"shared":{"lobby":false,"countdownRunning":false,"countdownEnd":false},"volumeConfig":{"global":60,"lobby":60,"countdownRunning":60,"countdownEnd":60,"useGlobalVolume":true},"titleConfig":{"lobby":"Song3","countdownRunning":"Song1","countdownEnd":"Song1"}},"nicks":{"memberGroups":[],"maxMembersPerGroup":10,"autoJoinToGroup":false,"selectedNicks":[],"blockIllegalNicks":true}},"state":"Inactive","currentStartTimestamp":-1}